#### About me

Adviser/Influencer mindset, with over 10 years of experience in Support Services and IT roles. I have honed advanced critical thinking and problem-solving skills, allowing me for an efficient and seamless adaptation to new environments. My background encompasses Support services, data analysis, Access administration, and Project Management. Currently, I am actively involved in global support projects related to Celergo Payroll Processing, including Data Integration Services, Process Model, Methodology, SLAs, and RCA analysis. And familiarized with Power BI reporting..

I am an enthusiast of blockchain, IoT, and Big Data. Captivated by their revolutionary potential to reshape industries and unlock unprecedented possibilities.

#### **Professional Experiences**

#### Global Service Support Representative at ADP

March, 2021 - Present

GSS Team Specialist - SME in Celergo payroll processing and support. Team Representative, working in collaboration with cross-functional teams, employing an iterative and incremental project management approach for Transitions to Service and Support.

Participating in CS teams projects: Service Catalog/Scope, Transition to Service, Service Readiness, monitoring. And sharing knowledge management with internal teams by sharing communications, training and Documentation related to Process Model, new enhancements and releases..

Managing internal team queues and ensuring adherence to SLA timelines and priorities, particularly in escalations.

Collaborating actively in data integration projects(WFN, WD, Oracle) Monitoring Live Client data integration errors, reporting technical failures, SORs configuration/update, Escalating Implementation issues and documenting RCAs

Performing data analysis and modeling, extracting insights and generating reports for team performance and SRs internal stats.

Communicating findings, publishing documentation, and providing recommendations to stakeholders.

Collaborating with the Products team. Providing system support and configuration training. Additionally, assisting in knowledge transfer, new releases and service transition sessions.

More projects: Access Request escalations, GDPR Data Purge, Payroll Integration configuration..

IT Support Analyst - T2 at Computacenter (Airbus)

July, 2014 - July, 2020

#### **Abdel Chafii**

Global Service Support Representative

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ abdelchafii/ abdel.chafii@outlook.co m

Barcelona (08014) Spain (+34) 662118064

# Skills & Knowledge

ADP HR systems - WFN

Database Systems: Oracle, Workday, Successfactors

**Microsoft Dynamics CRM** 

Power BI

**Active Directory** 

Ticketing Systems: Jira Service Management, Siebel, Remedy

Packet Tracer

Networking

**Data Integration** 

**Admin Console Portals** 

Sharepoint & Confluence

**Basic SAP skills** 

Microsoft Office - Excel

HTML & CSS

Technical & Functional skills

My role as T2 was focused on Providing Support to L1 Analysts and covering Escalations and High priority SRs for Airbus Account Admin/VIP users, managing access requests, and resolving errors related to Microsoft Office, Network cases, Active Directory, and SAP transactions errors reports. I am skilled in analyzing and troubleshooting technical issues, documenting solutions. My proficiency in these areas has enabled me to be in collaboration with Account Management, Quality and Training teams.

#### IT Support Analyst at Computacenter (Air Liquide)

April 2013 - July 2014

During my time As an IT Analyst, I possessed strong technical support skills with specialization in incident resolution, backlog management, access authentication, and Microsoft Office support. I excelled in providing customer support through various channels like chat, phone, and email. Multilingual Support for EN, SP, and FR speakers. Additionally, I was familiar with ticketing systems and user Portals.

#### **Booking/Support Team Agent at Avis Budget Group International**

March, 2021 - Present

Booking Agent for Renet CAR Service Desk, my responsibilities included handling bookings and Cards sale while ensuring compliance with relevant legislation by countries. I also provided support to customers by addressing queries and resolving issues related to their bookings or loyalty program.

#### **Education**

Law from Human Science Hassan II University - Casablanca 1998 - 2000 Master Not completed

Hostelry from ISTA - OFPPT 2000 - 2002

### Languages

English, French, Spanish, Catalan and Arabic

## Courses & Certifications

ADP - Celergo Learning Path

Agile Scrum Master Certification Training

Oracle Cloud Infrastructure - Certified Foundations Associate -Udemy

Data Integration Fundamentals - Udemy

Oracle Data Integrator (ODI) 12c Developer Course

AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials

Cybersecurity Essentials - Cisco Academy

Introduction to Packet Tracer - Cisco Academy

**Cloud Computing - Google** 

Chat GPT courses - Udemy

NDG Linux Essentials - Cisco Academy

